<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    <!--Fragment Titles-->
    <string name="title_history">HISTORY</string>
    <string name="title_attraction">ATTRACTION</string>
    <string name="title_icons">ICONS</string>
    <string name="title_street_food">STREET FOOD</string>

    <!--History Fragment-->
    <string name="Badshahi_Mosque">Badshahi Mosque</string>
    <string name="Badshahi_Mosque_Address">Walled City of Lahore, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Chauburji">Chauburji</string>
    <string name="Chaburji_address">Block B New Chauburji Park, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Haveli_Nau_Nihal_singh">Haveli Nau Nihal Singh</string>
    <string name="haveli_Nau_Nihal_singh_address">Mori Gali Bazar, Mohalla Sathan Walled City of Lahore, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Hiran_Minar">Hiran Minar</string>
    <string name="Hiran_Minar_address">Hiran Minar Park Rd, Sheikhupura, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Jahangir_tomb">Jahangir Tomb</string>
    <string name="Jahangir_tomb_address">Shahdara Town, Shahdara, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Lahore_Fort">Lahore Fort</string>
    <string name="Lahore_fort_address">Fort Rd, Walled City of Lahore, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Lohari_gate">Lohari Gate</string>
    <string name="Lohari_gate_address">227 Circular Rd, Jogi Mohalla Mohalla Chiri Maran Walled City of Lahore, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Moti_Masjid">Moti Masjid</string>
    <string name="Moti_Masjid_address">Walled City of Lahore, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Sheesh_mahal">Sheesh Mahal</string>
    <string name="Sheesh_mahal_address">Walled City of Lahore, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Tomb_Allama_iqbal">Tomb of Allama Iqbal</string>
    <string name="Tomb_iqbal_address">Outside Badshahi Mosque، Walled City of Lahore, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Tomb_anarkali">Tomb of Anarkali</string>
    <string name="Tomb_anarkali_address">Islampura, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Tomb_Nur_jahan">Tomb of Nur Jahan</string>
    <string name="Tomb_Nur_jahan_address">Shahdara Town, Shahdara, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>

    <!--Attraction Fragment-->
    <string name="Eiffel_tower_replica">Eiffel Tower Replica</string>
    <string name="Eiffel_tower_address">Bahria Town Main Blvd, Violet Block Bahria Town, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Emporium_mall">Emporium Mall</string>
    <string name="Emporium_address">16M Abdul Haque Rd, Trade Centre Commercial Area Phase 2 Johar Town, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Food_street">Food Street</string>
    <string name="Food_street_address">Walled City, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Grand_mosque">Grand Jamia Masjid</string>
    <string name="Grand_masjid_address">Bahria Town Main Blvd, Juniper Block Janiper Block Sector C Bahria Town, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Lahore_museum">Lahore Museum</string>
    <string name="Lahore_museum_address">Mall Rd, Anarkali Bazaar Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Lahore_zoo">Lahore Zoo</string>
    <string name="Lahore_zoo_address">92 - Shahrah-e-Quaid-e-Azam, The، Mall Rd, Jubilee Town, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Minar_e_Pakistan">Minar e Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Minar_e_Pakistan_address">Circular Rd, Walled City of Lahore, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Shalimar_Bagh">Shalimar Bagh</string>
    <string name="Shalimar_bagh_address">Shalamar Chowk، G. T. Road, Shalamar Town, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Data_darbar">Data Darbar</string>
    <string name="Data_darbar_address">Data Darbar Rd, Data Gunj Buksh Town, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Wazir_khan">Masjid Wazir Khan</string>
    <string name="wazir_khan_address">Shahi Guzargah، Dabbi Bazar, Chota Mufti Baqar Walled City of Lahore, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>

    <!--Icons Fragment-->
    <string name="Ammanullah_khan">Ammanullah Khan</string>
    <string name="Ammanullah_khan_bio">Amanullah Khan, known professionally as Amanullah, was a Pakistani Punjabi theatre performer, comedian and TV artist regarded as one of the best comedians in the Indian subcontinent.</string>
    <string name="Nusrat_fateh_ali_khan">Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan</string>
    <string name="Nusrat_bio">Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan, born Pervez Fateh Ali Khan, was a Pakistani vocalist, musician and music director primarily a singer of Qawwali, a form of Sufi Islamic devotional music.</string>
    <string name="Abrarul_haq">Abrar ul Haq</string>
    <string name="abrarul_haq_bio">Abrar-ul-Haq is a Pakistani politician, philanthropist and singer-songwriter. His debut 1995 album Billo De Ghar sold over 40.3 million albums worldwide, which made him a household name and granted him the title of "King of Pakistani Pop". </string>
    <string name="Ali_zafar">Ali Zafar</string>
    <string name="Ali_zafar_bio">Ali Zafar is a Pakistani singer-songwriter, model, actor, producer, screenwriter and painter. Zafar started out on Pakistani TV before becoming a popular musician. He later also established a career in Bollywood and his success led many Pakistani actors to venture into Hindi films.</string>
    <string name="Atif_aslam">Atif Aslam</string>
    <string name="Atif_aslam_bio">Muhammad Atif Aslam is a Pakistani playback singer and actor. He has recorded numerous chart-topping songs and is known for his vocal belting technique.</string>
    <string name="Amrita_pritam">Amrita Pritam</string>
    <string name="Amrita_pritam_bio">Amrita Pritam was an Indian novelist, essayist and poet, who wrote in Punjabi and Hindi. She is considered the first prominent female Punjabi poet, novelist, essayist and the leading 20th-century poet of the Punjabi language, who is equally loved on both sides of the India–Pakistan border.</string>
    <string name="Ashfaq_ahmad">Ashfaq Ahmad</string>
    <string name="Ashfaq_ahmad_bio">Ashfaq Ahmed was a writer, playwright and broadcaster from Pakistan. He wrote several books in Urdu. His works included novels, short stories and plays for television and radio of Pakistan. </string>
    <string name="faiz_ahmad_faiz">Faiz Ahmad Faiz</string>
    <string name="faiz_bio">Faiz Ahmad Faiz was a Pakistani Marxist, poet, and author in Urdu. He was one of the most celebrated writers of the Urdu language in Pakistan. </string>
    <string name="habib_jalib">Habib Jalib</string>
    <string name="habib_jalib_bio">Habib Jalib was a Pakistani revolutionary poet, left-wing activist and politician who opposed martial law, authoritarianism and state oppression. </string>
    <string name="Nawaz_sharif">Nawaz Sharif</string>
    <string name="nawaz_bio">Mian Muhammad Nawaz Sharif is a Pakistani businessman and politician who served as the prime minister of Pakistan for three non-consecutive terms. Sharif is the longest-serving prime minister of Pakistan having served a total of more than 9 years.</string>
    <string name="Imran_khan">Imran Khan</string>
    <string name="imran_bio">Imran Ahmed Khan Niazi HI PP is the 22nd and current Prime Minister of Pakistan and the chairman of the Pakistan Tehreek-e-Insaf. Before entering politics, Khan was an international cricketer and captain of the Pakistan national cricket team.</string>
    <string name="Mian_mansha">Mian Muhammad Mansha</string>
    <string name="mansha_bio">Mian Muhammad Mansha is a Pakistani business magnate and billionaire. He is the founder and CEO of the Lahore-based international conglomerate Nishat Group. </string>
    <string name="Sajal_aly">Sajal Aly</string>
    <string name="Sajal_bio">Sajal Aly is a Pakistani actress noted for playing a variety of characters in a range of serials—from contemporary social to romantic dramas.</string>
    <string name="Iman_Ali">Iman Ali</string>
    <string name="Iman_ali_bio">Iman Ali, is a highest paid Pakistani actress and veteran model who appears in Urdu films. Ali made her film debut with a leading role in the 2007 thriller film Khuda Kay Liye, for which she won a Lux Style Award for Best Actress.</string>
    <string name="Babar_azam">Babar Azam</string>
    <string name="Babar_azam_bio">Mohammad Babar Azam is a Pakistani cricketer who is captain of the Pakistan national team in Twenty20 internationals and vice-captain in One Day International matches. He is ranked No.1 on the ICC T20I Rankings for batsmen, No.3 in ODIs and No.5 in Tests. He is a right-handed top-order batsman.</string>
    <string name="Wasim_akram">Wasim Akram</string>
    <string name="Wasim_akram_bio">Wasim Akram is a Pakistani cricket commentator, coach and former cricketer, captain of Pakistan national cricket team. He is widely acknowledged as one of the greatest bowlers of all time.</string>

    <!--Street Food Fragment-->
    <string name="Chicken_Karahi_">Chicken Karahi (specifically Butt Karahi!)</string>
    <string name="butt_karahi_address">Gita Bhavan Building 18/3 , Laxmi Chowk، McLeod Rd, Royal Park, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Nihari">Muhammdi Nihari</string>
    <string name="nihari_address">Mian Mehmood Ali Kasoori Rd, Block A3 Block A 3 Gulberg III, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="halwa_puri">Halwa Puri from Taj Mahal Sweets</string>
    <string name="halwa_puri_address">Ali Park, 4 Fort Rd, Shahi Mohallah Walled City of Lahore, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="paye">Paaye from Manoo Siri Paaye</string>
    <string name="paye_address">Sultan Pura Rd, Sultan Pura Sultanpura Misri Shah, Lahore, Punjab</string>
    <string name="Falooda">Falooda from Baba Ji Kulfi Walay</string>
    <string name="Falooda_address">Ferozpur Rd, Muslim Town Mor, Muslim Town, Fazlia Colony, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Hareesa">Hareesa by Amritsari Hareesa</string>
    <string name="hareesa_address">37, Nisbat Rd, Qila Gujar Singh, Gawal Mandi, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Taka_Tak">Taka Tak from Cafe Riaz</string>
    <string name="TakaTak_address">Mini Market, Samanabad Town, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Ice_cream">Chaman Ice Cream</string>
    <string name="ice_cream_address">Beadon Rd, Garhi Shahu, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Shami_burger">Rangeela Burger</string>
    <string name="Shami_burger_address">Main Mall Road Near Naqi Market, Punjab, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Samosay">Samosa Cholay</string>
    <string name="samosay_address">Ghalib Market Gulberg III, Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan</string>

</resources>
